"反应炉3分钟后就要爆炸了
"We've got three minutes till the reactor blows.
我们逃不掉了"
We'll never make it!"
"你得赶快逃命  救你自己"
"You've got to get out of here! Save yourself!"
"不行  我不会扔下你"
"No, I won't leave you."
"别管我   我是机器人  我只是一台机器"
"Don't worry about me. I'm a robot. I'm just a machine!"
"不  对我来说  不是"   天哪
"No, you're not. Not to me." Oh, my God.
怎么样   我真的太有天份了
What? I am extremely talented.
对  你的确很棒啊
Yeah. You're great. Yeah.
好  让我们接着从  我是说  我真的演得很带劲
Okay, let's take it from... No, I mean, I was really acting my ass off.
我觉得我演的也不错
I thought I was pretty good too.
对  你跟个石头似的  你不如我
Yeah, you're solid. You're just no me.
我看就先这样吧
You know what? I think that's enough for now.
我不想排练过头
I don't want to be over-rehearsed. Ha-ha-ha.
没关系   我一个人自己演
Fine. I'll do it without you!
没你或其它人  我照样演
I don't need you or anybody else!
我会靠自己成功的
I'm gonna make it on my own!
等着瞧   你们都给我等着瞧吧
You'll see! You'll all see!
老友记  第六季  第20集  试镜风波
Friends  S06E20  The One With Mac and C.H.E.E.S.E.
主演: 珍妮佛·安妮斯顿
主演: 寇妮·考克斯
主演: 丽莎·库卓
主演: 麦特·勒布兰
主演: 马修·派瑞
主演: 大卫·修蒙
这次  你要去试什么镜
So, what's this thing you're auditioning for?
是一部新电视节目
It's a new TV show. Yeah.
我的角色叫麦克麦可维利  也叫"麦克"
I'm up for the part of Mac, Machiavelli, or "Mac"!
我是个侦探   将和我的机器人拍档一起  打击犯罪
I'm a detective and I solve crimes with the help of my robot partner.
他是具有人工智能的
He's a computerized, humanoid...
电子增强型的秘密特工
...electronically enhanced secret enforcer.
简称 "吉事"
Or, "C.H.E.E.S.E."
所以就是麦克与吉事   就是那剧名
So, Mac and C.H.E.E.S.E.? That's the title!
幸好缩写刚好是 "吉事"
They really lucked out that the initials spell "cheese."
真是幸运啊
That is lucky.
乔伊  要是你拿到这个角色
Huh. Wait so Joey, if you get this, you're gonna be, like...
就有你自己成名的电视节目了
...the star of your own TV show.
你就会被称为大吉事（汉堡）或是大麦克（麦香堡）都是你的最爱啊
I mean, you'll be like the "Big Cheese" or the "Big Mac." Hey, you love those!
别抱太大期望   可能没那么好
Well, don't get your hopes up, because probably not gonna happen.
你为什么要这么说   约瑟芬
Now-now, why would you say that, Joseph?
拜托   伙计们  我自己的电视节目
Well, I mean, come on, you guys. My own TV show? I just...
我都不知道我自己行不行  我行
I don't know if I'm good enough. I am. Heh.
乔伊  你在说什么  你是个很棒的演员
Joey, What are you talking about? You're a terrific actor.
真的吗   你怎么能这么问
You really think so? How can you even ask that question?
她真的漂亮   对  人也很好
She's pretty. Yeah. And she's really nice too.
她教我怎么面对镜头
She taught me all about, you know, how to work with cameras...
还有如何 "掩饰尴尬"
...and "smell the fart" acting.
抱歉  什么  乔伊  抱歉
I'm sorry, what'd you say? Joey, Excuse me?
就像你一下要背很多台词
It's like, you got so many lines to learn so fast...
有时得停下来想下一句
...that sometimes you need a minute to remember your next one.
在你想的时候  要来个大停顿  表情专注故作严肃
So while you're thinking of it, you take this big pause where you look all intense.
就像这样来掩饰
You know, like this:
好  懂了
Oh. Okay.
该我了   该我了
Here's my scene! Here's my scene!
华勒斯太太  我是雷莫瑞医生  令妹的神经外科医生
Mrs. Wallace? I'm Dr. Drake Ramoray, your sister's neurosurgeon.
令妹得了一种
You sister is suffering from a...
伊娃   我们合作得很愉快
Well, Eva, we've done some excellent work here.
而且我要说  你的问题很明显了
And I would have to say, your problem is quite clear.
All you want is a dingle
What you envy's a schwang
A thing through which you can tinkle
Or play with or simply let hang
我演艾尔帕西诺的屁股
I play Al Pacino's butt.
怎么样  他进去淋浴  然后我就是他的屁股
All right? He goes into the shower and then, I'm his butt.
天哪   别这样  伙计们
Oh, my God. Come on, you guys.
这是一部艾尔帕西诺主演的真正的电影  是部大制作
This is a real movie and Al Pacino's in it, and that's big!
的确很棒  你当之无愧   努力了这么久
No, it's terrific. You deserve this after all your years of struggling...
终于可以 "屁美" 别人了
...you've finally been able to crack your way into show business.
好  你们尽管笑吧  我不在乎  这是我千载难逢的机会
Okay, fine, make jokes. I don't care. This is a big break for me.
没错   你说得很对
No, you're right, it is. Yeah.
你会邀请我们去看你 "精屁"的演出吗
So, you gonna invite us all to the big opening?
好  我要走了  祝我好运
All right, I'm out of here. Wish me luck.
加油  加油  我们都祝你好运
Good luck, good luck We all wish you good luck
随便啦
Yeah, whatever.
该你了
It's your turn.
我们在玩吗
Oh, are we playing this?
嘿  嘿  试镜还顺利吗
Hey. Hey. How did the audition go?
糟透了  我把台词都念错了  我不该当演员的
Terrible. I messed up every line. I shouldn't even be an actor.
等等  你又在假装不顺利了
Wait a minute, are you doing that thing where you pretend it didn't go well...
其实很顺利吧
...but it really did go well?
对  你们上过当了吗  完全被骗了
Yeah, did I fool you? Totally!
所以  一切很顺利   顺利的不得了
So, it did go well? It went amazingly well!
太好了  太好了
Great. That's great.
只剩下我和另外两个人  天哪
Yeah-yeah, It's down to me and two other guys. Oh, my God.
而且我认识他们两个  那两个人都很厉害
And I know both of them, and they're really good.
其中一个就是在过敏广告里  被巨无霸花朵
One of them is the guy from those allergy commercials who's always being chased...
追来追去的人  我好喜欢那个人
...by those big flowers. Oh, I love that guy.
你在干什么
Oh. What are you doing?
我在干什么
What am I doing?
我好紧张  明天下午5点才要复试
I'm so nervous, you know? The callback isn't till tomorrow at 5.
我感到头都要炸了
I feel like my head's gonna explode.
对啊   你的头早该爆了
Well, it is overdue.
放心  好吗  你一定没问题
Don't worry, okay? You're gonna be fine.
对   但压力太大了
Yeah, but it's so much pressure.
很抱歉   但你们所面临的和我不一样
I mean no offense, but what you guys all do is very different.
我不知道你们能不能体会
I don't know if you'd understand.
是啊  我们的工作都没有压力
Yeah, none of the rest of us have to deal with pressure at our jobs.
是的  我知道现在几点了
Yes, I know what time it is...
但是我正在看财务报表   不满意
...but I'm looking at the WENIS and I'm not happy.
好了  我在撕生菜
Well, I'm tearing the lettuce.
很脏吗  不  放心  我会洗干净的
Uh-huh? Is it dirty? No, don't worry, I'm gonna wash it.
不必了   我喜欢它脏点
Don't. I like it dirty.
你决定就好
That's your call.
你接下来要做什么
So, uh, what are you going to do next?
我想我要切蕃茄了
Well, I thought that I would cut up the tomatoes.
它们结实吗
Are they firm?
还可以
They're all right.
你确定它们还没坏掉   你确定它们没有坏透嘛
You sure they haven't gone bad? You sure they're not very, very bad?
没有  真的  它们还好
No, really. They're okay.
你会把它们切得很漂亮吗
You gonna slice them up real nice?
其实  我想把它们切成条
Ahem. Actually, I was gonna do them julienne.
我要走了
I'm out of here.
摩妮卡  我要辞职  我刚帮了一个81岁的老太太系上皮带
Monica, I'm quitting. I just helped an 81-year-old woman put on a thong...
而她竟然根本没买
...and she didn't even buy it.
我要辞职   就这样   我现在就要跟老板说
I'm telling you I'm quitting. That's it. I'm talking to my boss right now.
没错  我马上就去  马上就去
Yes, I am. Yes, I am.
再见  听到留言请回电
Okay, bye. Call me when you get this message.
怎么了
Well, what happened?
他来按摩  本来挺好的  可是后来
Well, he came in for a massage, and everything was fine until...
天哪
Oh, my God.
然后突然间  他动手动脚也不算啥了
And all of a sudden, his hands weren't the problem anymore.
他有没有   他那儿用来搭帐棚都绰绰有余了
Was it? Oh, Boy Scouts could've camped under there.
你吃了我的三明治
You ate my sandwich.
纯粹是个失误   谁都可能会犯
It was a simple mistake. It could happen to anyone.
真的吗
Oh, really?
你别激动
Now calm down.
到我办公室来找   垃圾桶里可能还有
Come look in my office. Some of it may still be in the trash.
什么  它太大了
What? Well, it was quite large.
大部分都被我扔了
I had to throw most of it away.
你扔掉了我的三明治
You threw my sandwich away?
我的三明治
My sandwich?
My sandwich!
我很想拿到这个角色   你知道吗
It's just, I want this part so much, you know?
要是我没拿到  我就再也不吃起司通心面
If I don't get this part, I'm never gonna eat macaroni and cheese again.
不  我没那样说  那不算的
No, I didn't say that. That doesn't count.
别这样  各位  我又不是搬到欧洲去
Come on, guys. It's not like I moved to Europe.
我只是搬到对面
I just moved across the hall.
假如摩妮卡不会过敏
And we would have you over all the time...
你们随时能过来
...if it weren't for Monica's allergies.
没错   我骗不了你们
You're right, I could never lie to you.
她讨厌你们
She hates you.
我该接吗
Should I get that? Ha-ha-ha.
喂  不  乔伊现在不在
Hello? Uh, no, Joey's not here right now.
你要留言吗
Can I take a message?
好  试镜从5点改到2点半
Yeah, okay. So the audition's been moved from 5 to 2:30?
好的  再见
Okay, great. Bye.
你还没穿衣服   我又光着身子了
Aren't you dressed yet? Am I naked again?
我们15分钟后要去见我爸妈
We're supposed to meet my parents in 15 minutes.
好  我只是在跟他们聊天  你看他们嘛
Okay. I was just talking to the guys. Just look at them.
我的意思是   他们可以去找我们吗
I mean, is it okay if they come visit?
那我的过敏怎么办
What about my allergies?
对啊   你会过敏
Right. Your allergies.
都是她   她讨厌你们
All her. She hates you.
漂亮
Yes! All right.
要是这些小人能变成真人大小  那该有多酷啊
How cool would it be if you could watch like a real life-size version of this?
我是说该有多过瘾啊   跟足球一样过瘾
I mean, how crazy would that be? As crazy as soccer?
喂
Hello?
你在说什么  不是5点才试镜嘛
What are you talking about? The audition's not till 5.
没有人告诉我啊
Well, nobody told me.
你跟谁说的
Who'd you talk to?
没事
Never mind.
你是说你没有看到我的留言吗
You mean you didn't get it from this?
那个患有敏感症的家伙入选了   谢谢你啊
The allergy guy got the part. Thanks.
也许我们能补救   你知道吗
Well, maybe we can fix it, you know?
也许我们能送巨无霸大花去吓吓他
Maybe we can send him some big, big flowers and scare him!
你怎么能这样对我   钱德
How could you do this to me Chandler?!
这个角色能扭转我的整个演艺生涯
This part could've turned my whole career around.
是我的错  对不起  我真的搞砸了
I messed up, okay? I'm sorry. I really messed up.
你都已经不住在这里了  干嘛要接听我的电话
You don't even live here anymore. Why'd you answer my phone?
我可以录音的  是我买给你的
I have a machine! Which I bought for you.
还教你怎么用   你还以为它是复印机
Taught you how to use it. You thought it was a copier.
我愿意尽全力挽救这个错误   我一定会做  知道吗
If there was anything I could do, I would do it, okay?
但是人起码可以犯一次错错  不是吗
But everybody's allowed one mistake, right?
他可以送我录影机  或是一对高尔夫球杆
He could have gotten me a VCR. He could have gotten me golf clubs.
可是  他偏偏要送我这个  吓跑女人
But no, he has to get me the woman repeller.
看着碍眼  戴着碍事儿的东西
The eyesore from the Liberace House of Crap!
没那么严重啦  你当然说得容易了
it's not that bad. Oh, yeah, easy for you to say.
你又不必戴着  被某个老粗淘汰的金饰到处跑
You don't have to walk around sporting some reject from the Mr. T Collection.
钱德  钱德
Chandler. Chandler.
我真同情戴这个手饰的人  真的
I pity the fool who puts on my jewelry! I do! I do!
我真同情戴这个  你好
I pity the fool that--
嘿
Hi.
你昨晚迟到后   凯西和我聊了起来  然后
When you were late last night, Kathy and I got to talking and...
事情演变到后来就
...one thing led to another and...
就什么  你跟她上床
And what? Did you sleep with her?
没有  我只是吻了她  什么  那更糟
No! No, I just kissed her. What? That's even worse!
怎么会更糟   我不知道  反正都一样
How is that worse? I don't know! But it's the same!
你说得对  我无话可说  我太过分了
You're right, I have no excuses. I was totally over the line.
"过分"
"Over the line?"
你根本就过分到  连过分见到你
You're so far past the line that you can't even see the line!
都会说你过分
Yeah, the line is a dot to you!
我不奢望你马上原谅我
Look, I'm not saying that you should magically forgive me.
但你也不完美   你也做过错误的判断
But you're not perfect. You've made some errors in judgment too.
举个例子
Name one.
怎么回事
What happened?
他答应不拿沙发椅的
Aw, man! He promised he wouldn't take the chairs!
怎么回事   你怎么会被关进去呢
What the hell happened? How were you locked in?
我们的东西呢
And where the hell's all of our stuff?
有一个人过来看柜子
Well, this guy came by to look at the unit...
他说他不相信能塞下一个大人
...and he said he didn't think big enough to fit a grown man.
所以  你就自愿进去
So you got in voluntarily?
我想把柜子卖出去嘛
I was trying to make a sale!
要是让我碰上他  你猜我会怎样
Oh, man, if I ever run into that guy again, you know what I'm gonna do?
把屁股翘起来
Bend over?
她来了
There's Lorraine.
记住  不准交换  美女是你的  失恋女是我的
Okay, now remember, no trading. You get the pretty one, I get the mess.
嗨  乔伊  嘿
Hi, Joey. Hey.
他就是你带来的人
Well, well. Look what you brought.
你又带谁来了
And what did you bring?
她在寄放外套
She's checking her coat.
乔伊   我要去洗个手
Joey, I'm gonna go wash the cab smell off my hands.
你帮我叫一杯白酒   帮珍妮丝叫一杯红酒
Will you get me a white Zinfandel and a glass of red for Janice?
珍妮丝
Janice?
我的天哪
Oh, my God!
乔伊的栽缝吃我豆腐
Joey's tailor took advantage of me.
什么
What?
不可能   我找他做了12年衣服
No way. I've been going to the guy for 12 years.
拜托啦   他说要量裤管内侧
He said he was gonna do my inseam...
然后他的手一路摸上来   然后就
...then he ran his hand up my leg and then there was definite...
怎样
What?
包住了
Cupping.
裤子就是那样量的
That's how they do pants!
罗斯  你告诉他
Ross, will you tell him?
裤子不都是那样量的  是啊  是啊  在监狱里
Isn't that how a tailor measures pants? Yes, yes, it is. In prison!
叫你举一个就好
I said name one!
我居然这么粗心  我真白痴  别再自责了
I can't believe I did this. What an idiot. Stop beating yourself up.
人都会犯错   这是难免的
People make mistakes. These things happen.
你没有忘记帮我记留言吧
There aren't any messages you've forgotten to give me, are there?
显然  你不太会记留言
Apparently, you're not very good at it.
你们觉得他会原谅我吗  当然会
Do you think he'll ever forgive me? Of course he will.
钱德  但最重要的是  你得原谅自己
Chandler, the most important thing is that you forgive yourself.
其实我已经原谅自己了  这么快
You know what, I kind of have. Already?
你犯的错蛮严重的
That was pretty bad, what you did.
你知道吗  他会原谅你的
You know what? He will forgive you.
我接电话时都会带便条纸  以防万一  好啦
And I like to bring a pad with me when I go answer the phone, just in case. Okay.
你没看到他气成什么样子
You didn't see how mad he was, you know?
他一定会原谅你的
I'm sure he will forgive you.
我们都有这种经验  吵架  和解
Look, we've all been there, you know? You fight, you make up.
就是这样
That's the way it works.
感情破裂  往往是两个人的错
It took two people to break up this relationship!
对  你和复印店那个女的
Yeah! You and that girl from the copy place...
你昨天表明愿意负责
...which yesterday you took full responsibility for!
我不知道我负的是什么责
I didn't know what I was taking responsibility for, okay?
我没把信看完
I didn't finish the whole letter.
什么   我睡着了
What? I fell asleep.
你睡着了
You fell asleep?
当时是早上5点半
It was 5:30 in the morning.
你一废话就废话了十八页
And you had rambled on for 18 pages.
正反面都写满了
Front and back!
还有 "你得"是指 "你必须"
And by the way? Y-O-U, apostrophe R-E means, "you are."
"你的"是所有格
Y-O-U-R means "your."
我居然想要跟你复合
Y'know I can't believe I thought of getting back together with you.
我们根本就完了
We are so over!
无所谓
Fine by me!
顺便告诉你   那种事并不常见
And hey! just so you know, it's not that common...
不是男人都会那样   没有什么大不了的
...it doesn't happen to every guy, and it is a big deal!
我就知道
I knew it!
你没有权利和他约会   这真是太荒谬了
You had no right to go out with him. That is the most ridiculous--
你出卖了我   我没有出卖你
You sold me out! I did not sell you out!
不  你出卖了  你当然出卖了我   你还让我说话吗
Yes, you did! You absolutely sold me-Would you let me talk?
你弹了我的额头吗
Did you just flick me?
你不让我说完   我只是想  我很
Okay, well, you wouldn't let me finish and I was just-Ow!
够了  够了
Stop it! Ow! Ow!
住手  住手
stop. Stop.
好  不要这样  不要啊
All right. No, let's not do this. No!
想想快乐的事   不
Happy thoughts. No!
别打了
Stop it! Oh! Oh!
好了   我就要踢屁股了
Okay, now I'm gonna kick some ass!
痛  痛  我知道
Ow. Ow. Ow. I know, I know.
好  你们住手  我就放手
All right. Now, I will let go if you both stop.
好吧  好吧
Fine. Fine.
这样多好
There we go.
你知道吗   如果在监狱  你们就是我的喽罗了
Ha. You know what? If we were in prison, you guys would be like my bitches.
好吗   兄弟   你瞧瞧怎么样
Okay, buddy boy, here it is.
你敢藏我的衣服    我就把你衣服都穿上
You hide my clothes? I'm wearing everything you own.
我的天哪
Oh, my God!
看啊  我是钱德   我还能再多穿点衣服吗
Look at me, I'm Chandler! Could I be wearing any more clothes?
或许我要去玩野战游戏
Maybe if I wasn't going "commando."
穿这么多衣服真热   我最好别蹲什么弓箭步
Yeah. Whew, it's hot with all of this stuff on. I better not do any, I don't know, lunges.
I think of all the friends I know
When I dial the telephone
no one's home
How by myself
Don't wanna leave how by myself
and how by myself
乔伊
Joey?
给你买了乔伊套餮   两个披萨
Got you the Joey special. Two pizzas!
乔伊
Joey?
喂  又来了
Hello? Damn it!
喂
Hello?
乔伊现在不在   我可以帮你留言吧
No, Joey's not here right now, but I can take a message. I think.
他还有机会得到那个角色   真是个好消息
He's still got a chance for the part? Oh, That's great news!
很明显不是因为  那位被狗咬伤的演员而幸灾乐祸
Well, no, obviously not for the actor who was mauled by his dog.
太好了  我会转告乔伊   谢谢
Oh well, that's great. I will give Joey the message. Thank you.
漂亮
Yes!
好
0Kay.
麦克
Mac...
试镜
...audition...
2点钟
...at 2.
过敏
Allergy...
演员
...actor...
遭攻击
...attacked.
被狗
By dog...
不是
...not...
被花
...flowers.
请告诉我   你有收到留言
Hey. Please tell me you got the message.
什么留言  要演麦克的演员不能演了
What message? The actor playing Mac couldn't do it.
他们要你2点过去   什么   明明是6点
They needed to see you at 2:00. What? It's 6:00!
看  我写了  我写在留言板上了
Look! I wrote it! I wrote it on the board!
我写在留言板上  然后跑遍整个纽约去找你
I wrote it on the board, then went looking all New York City looking for you!
我跑去罗斯家  跑去咖啡厅
I went to Ross's, I went to the coffee house.
跑去每一个有三明治的地方
I went to any place that they make sandwiches!
我不敢相信   钱德   对不起
I can't believe this, Chandler! I'm sorry.
我不知道该说什么
I don't know what to say!
那就说恭喜吧
Well you-you-you-you might say congratulations!
我看到留官板   跑去试镜   我拿到那角色了
I saw the board, I went to the audition, I got the part!
你觉得很好笑吗   我刚才真的很担心
Is that supposed to be funny? I was really worried over here.
抱歉   有时候这样骗人真的很恶劣
Oh, well I'm  sorry. Y'know, sometimes that fake out thing is just mean!
好  伙计  抱歉  我不是故意让你难受的
Okay, man. I'm sorry. I did not mean to make you feel bad.
哎  没什么
Well, that's good.
因为你不是有意的   我好替你高兴
Because you didn't. And I'm incredibly happy for you!
你好恶劣
That's mean!
是你告诉我去的   我们这样玩一整天都玩不完的
You had me going there! We could do this all day.
也对  没错
Yeah, you're right.
好吧  我们来聊聊我会有多红
Okay look, listen, let's talk about what a huge star I'm gonna be.
你会变成超级大明星  我要抱你
You are gonna be a huge star. I'm gonna hug you.
来抱吧  没问题
You hug me. All right.
You really gotta a hold on me
Baby! I love you
All I want you to do is just hold me
Please  squeeze me  hold me  hold me
我们会不会抱的太久了  我也觉得
Hey, do we do this too much? I think so.
放开我   就是啊
Yeah. Get off me. Yeah.
"吉事  我不会扔下你的
"Come on, C.H.E.E.S.E., I'm not leaving without you.
你从中央处理器   启动备用电源"
Try routing your backup power source through your primary CPU."
"没办法  我的电路烧焦了 它们烧焦了  我告诉你"
"I can't! My circuits are fried! They're fried, I tell you!"
"那我就背你"
"Well, then I'll just have to carry you."
"好棒的招数啊
"That'll be a neat trick...
等你死了再说"
...when you're dead!"
罗斯  你不必用喊的
Ross, you don't have to yell.
刚才有爆炸   我的听力可能会受损
There was just an explosion, okay? My hearing would be impaired.
我觉得你很棒
I thought you were excellent.
其实有几分钟我一直在想   我甚至觉得"罗斯怎么还不出场"
In fact, for a minute there, I was like, "Ooh, where did Ross go?"
谢谢了   我想说你和麦克见面的第一场戏
Thank you. And I have to say that first scene where you meet Mae...
怎么样   我的天哪   我是说
Yeah. Oh, my God. I mean...
你们知道吗
You know what?
今天就到此为止了   多谢你们的帮忙
I think that's enough for today. Thanks for your help.
他拖我们后腿了  就是啊
Holding us back. Totally.